Contact

abhaydev837@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abhay-dev-6167b7156 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Project Planning Communication Team Leadership

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Malayalam (Native or Bilingual)
Hindi (Limited Working)

Certifications

Initiating and planning projects
Certified Information Systems
Security Specialist
Managing Talent

Introduction to Cybersecurity Tools & Cyber Attacks

Introduction to Cybersecurity Tools & Cyber Attacks

Honors-Awards

Linux workshop

IEEE- Microsoft App development Campaign

Stratup simulation game

Publications

The Approaches and Uses of the Balanced Scorecard - A Comparitive Study

Abhay dev

HR operations & Talent acquisition at Crio.Do | MBA - HR,Operations | B.tech - ECE | Part time artist Ernakulam

Summary

I am a systematic and organized individual who has passion for HR. I move forward with the motivation that comes from within and I make it productive by giving everything I have got. During my free time I indulge in drawing and listen to music. I have been practicing yoga for the past few years and have gained preliminary training in Muay Thai(kickboxing). I am open to absorb any new skill which is relevant to my career. I am a person who loves to travel and experience new cultures and I am also friendly and kind towards everyone.

Experience

Crio.Do

HR operations & Talent acquisition Intern June 2020 - Present (3 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

- *Working closely with the founding members, understanding the organizations requirement and working accordingly.
- * Hiring computer engineers from top notch companies like Google, Microsoft, Amazon etc for Launch+ mock interview program.
- *Hiring for the role of teaching assistants from IIT, NIT and other top colleges in the country.
- *Managing a pool of Crio interviewers, handling their engagement,feedback etc.
- *Scheduling and monitoring almost 200 interviews per month.
- *Working on different programs like Launch+, Accelerate, Pilot interviews etc.
- *Tracking and updating various metrices and handling salary of Crio interviewers.

Mathrubhumi HR intern April 2019 - June 2019 (3 months) calicut

*I was asked to develop a robust performance management system for which I suggested a HR Scorecard

*Maintainance of employee data files

*Assisted in data collection and sorting for employee ID Card

*Assisted in sorting employee P.F data

*Assisted in recruitment process

Education

Amrita School of Business- Kochi
Master of Business Administration - MBA, HR Major and Operations
Minor · (2018 - 2020)

MES ENGINEERING COLLEGE, KUTTIPPURAM

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electronics and Communications

Engineering · (2011 - 2015)

fathima matha higher secondary school, Tirur

Mathematics, Biology, Physics, Chemistry, English and Hindi (2008 - 2010)

Fathima Matha English medium school matriculation · (2007 - 2008)